Héctor Olivares

Web Developer

& +52 55 1074 6206
☐ hectorolivares033@gmail.com ⊕ hectorolivares.me ☐ github.com/hectorolivares

About me

I am a web developer with experience in TypeScript, React, and Tailwind CSS. I am passionate about programming and always strive to stay up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies to improve my skills as a developer. I consider myself a very committed worker and enjoy collaborating with others to achieve common goals.

My goal as a web developer is to create innovative and efficient solutions to the problems that arise in software development. I see myself as a creative, analytical, and problem-solving person.

Skills

Programming languages

TypeScript, JavaScript(ES6), HTML, CSS/Scss/Sass, Python

Frameworks/Libraries/Others

React, Vue, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, Webpack, WordPress, Netlify, Vercel, NPM, Git, Command line

UX/UI Design

Responsive Design, Prototyping, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

Currently learning

Next.js, SQL, Java

Education

Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México (National Autonomous University of Mexico)

B.E. in Computer Engineering, with specialization in Software Engineering

August 2020 - Present

Projects

Bazar Yokai

Ecommerce project dedicated to promote and support local economies, as well as highlight special and unique products. Our main goal is to provide people with an online platform where they can easily showcase their work and sell their products effectively.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

Design and development of websites that help to advertise projects and/or businesses of the people who work with me.

July 2022 - Present

Languages

English (Intermediate) Spanish (Native)

Interests

App development, game development, digital content creation, running, football, sports, reading, movies, philosophy and architecture.

Héctor Olivares

Desarrollador web

& +52 55 1074 6206
☐ hectorolivares033@gmail.com ⊕ hectorolivares.me ☐ github.com/hectorolivares

Sobre mí

Soy un desarrollador web con experiencia en TypeScript, React y Tailwind CSS. Me apasiona la programación y siempre me esfuerzo por estar actualizado en las últimas tendencias y tecnologías para mejorar mis habilidades como desarrollador. Me considero una persona muy comprometida y disfruto colaborar con otros para alcanzar objetivos en común.

Mi objetivo como desarrollador web es crear soluciones innovadoras y eficientes para los problemas que surgen en el desarrollo de software. Me veo a mí mismo como una persona creativa, analítica y resolutiva.

Habilidades

Lenguajes de programación

TypeScript, JavaScript(ES6), HTML, CSS/Scss/Sass, Python

Frameworks/Librerias/Otros

React, Vue, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, Webpack, WordPress, Netlify, Vercel, NPM, Git, Command line

UX/UI Design

Responsive Design, Prototyping, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

Actualmente aprendiendo

Next.is, SQL, Java

Educación

Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, Facultad de Ingeniería

Ingeniería en Computación, con especialización en Ingeniería de Software.

Agosto 2020 - Presente

Proyectos

Bazar Yokai

Proyecto de ecommerce dedicado a promover y apoyar las economías locales, así como destacar productos especiales y únicos. Nuestro objetivo principal es proporcionar a las personas una plataforma en línea donde puedan dar a conocer su trabajo de manera sencilla y vender sus productos de forma efectiva.

Experiencia

Desarrollador Web Freelance

Diseño y desarrollo de páginas web, que ayudan a publicitar proyectos y/o negocios de las personas que trabajan conmigo.

Julio 2022 - Presente

Idiomas

Inglés (Intermedio) Español (Nativo)

Intereses

Desarrollo de juegos, desarollo de apps, creación de contenido digital, correr, fútbol, deportes, lectura, películas, filosofía y arquitectura.